livecap.tv 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy - TopCSGOBettingSites.com

At topcsgobettingsites.com we value your privacy as much as you do and we have created this Privacy Policy that ensures your peace of mind. Privacy Policy together with the Terms and Conditions sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting our site you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## What Information We Collect?

We collect different types of information from our Users: 

  * Information which you provide us voluntarily when you respond to communications from us or communicate with us via email such as first and last name, email address, gender.
  * We collect specific types of connection details and information with regard to your device, software or hardware that may identify you, such as: device’s unique identifiers (IMEI, MAC address), browser fingerprinting, IP address and geo-location data.

## How Is It Collected?

We collect information about you when you fill in a contact form or email us directly. We also can get non-Personal Information from Your device using various standard technologies, such as cookies, digital identifiers, log files or other similar technologies.

## Why Is It Being Collected?

We use information held about you to improve the quality and design of the Site, to email you about other services and information we think may be of interest to you. We may use cookies and log files information to personalize and customize your experience on our site and track your use to generate statistics.

## How will it be used?

We use your Personal Information for the purposes listed below:

  * To communicate with your and to process any of your requests to exercise your User Rights;
  * To set up, manage and update your account;
  * To perform research, technical diagnostics, analytics or statistical purposes;
  * To detect and prevent fraudulent and illegal activity;

## Who Will It Be Shared With?

We may appoint certain third parties including but not limited to analytics companies, advertising agencies, risk and fraud agencies or customer service agencies to process your personal data on our behalf. These third parties will only process your personal data in accordance with our instructions and we will ensure that adequate measures are in place to ensure that your personal data is processed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and kept secure at all times.

We may also share your information with third parties in the following situations:

  * If we think doing so is necessary to protect the rights, property, security, safety of us or our users.
  * Investigation and prevent fraudulent or illegal activity.

## Cookies

A 'cookie' is a small text file that is downloaded onto your Access Device when you visit a website and that enables the website to obtain certain information from your browser, such as your preferences. Cookies allow us to maximize your experience using the Website by increasing its functionality and allowing the Website to remember information and selections as you move from page to page and from a visit to visit, depending on the cookie. A cookie does not harm Your Access Device nor does it contain any viruses or other malware and also used to help ensure that the advertisements you see online are relevant to you and your interests.

Topcsgobettingsites.com uses cookies solely for the purpose of customizing pages during future visits in order to improve the user experience as well as our website content.

## Protection of Minors

Topcsgobettingsites.com is an online gambling information portal and as such none of its marketing content, products, services or promotions are appropriate for, or targeted at, children and visitors under the age of 18 years (or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction).

The Site bears no responsibility for the actions taken by children or visitors under the age of 18 based on the content found on Topcsgobettingsites.com, or any of its sub-domains and pages.

## What Are Your Rights?

You have a number of rights under data protection law in relation to the way we process your personal data. These are set out below:

  * A right to access personal data held by us about you.
  * Request further clarification as to our use of your personal information.
  * A right to require us to rectify any inaccurate personal data held by us about you.
  * A right to require us to erase personal data held by us about you.

## Third Party Services

While using Topcsgobettingsites.com you may encounter links to third party websites, services or applications. Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible, downloadable, or otherwise distributed through the this site.

Please be advised that such third party websites, services or applications are independent of topcsgobettingsites.com. We assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such third party websites. Carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use of such third party websites and/or services, as their terms, not ours, will apply to any of your interactions with such third parties.

You should always review their privacy practices carefully before providing Personal Information to such third parties.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will notify you in advance of any changes.  Please also ensure that you frequently check this Privacy Policy for any updates.

## Contact Us

If you have any general questions, comments and requests about Topcsgobettingsites.com or the information that we collect about you and how we use it, please contact us here.
